[{"answer": "What can I get for you", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Ill have a tall, double, non-fat, mocha cappuccino", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 13, "question": "What can I get for you", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Ill have a tall black coffee, please", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Ill have a tall, double, non-fat, mocha cappuccino", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Is that together or separate", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Ill have a tall black coffee, please", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Together.  Ill get it this time, Erin", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Is that together or separate", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " OK, its $7.50 please", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Together.  Ill get it this time, Erin", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 18, "question": " OK, its $7.50 please", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Thanks for the coffee, Rachel", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " No problem.  You got it last time", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Thanks for the coffee, Rachel", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " So what have you been up today", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 21, "question": " No problem.  You got it last time", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Not much.  Just surfin the net all morning", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 25, "question": " So what have you been up today", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Sounds exciting", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Not much.  Just surfin the net all morning", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Not really.  Actually, I did come across something interesting", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Sounds exciting", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Oh, yeah?  Whats that", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Not really.  Actually, I did come across something interesting", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Well, I was looking around for drink recipes to serve at my party this weekend", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Oh, yeah?  Whats that", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " What did it say", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Well, I was looking around for drink recipes to serve at my party this weekend", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " I cant remember all of the uses, but they were pretty funny.  Id never heard o", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 36, "question": " What did it say", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " You mean rub it all over yourself to keep the bugs away?  Youd get all messy", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 41, "question": " I cant remember all of the uses, but they were pretty funny.  Id never heard o", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " No.  You sprinkle them on the ground where you dont want bugs, like ants o", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 42, "question": " You mean rub it all over yourself to keep the bugs away?  Youd get all messy", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Oh, I see.  I was just imagining a person covered with brown coffee grounds", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 46, "question": " No.  You sprinkle them on the ground where you dont want bugs, like ants o", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " No, I dont think so.  Oh, another weird thing was that it said you could us", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Oh, I see.  I was just imagining a person covered with brown coffee grounds", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 51, "question": " No, I dont think so.  Oh, another weird thing was that it said you could us", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Well, it said after you shampoo your dog, you can rub coffee grounds into it", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 52, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Ive never heard of that before.  Your dog would smell like coffee", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Well, it said after you shampoo your dog, you can rub coffee grounds into it", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " I know.  Id never heard of it before either.  But I guess smelling like coffee i", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Ive never heard of that before.  Your dog would smell like coffee", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " True, I guess thats right.  Maybe Ill try it on Champ and see if his fur looks better", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 61, "question": " I know.  Id never heard of it before either.  But I guess smelling like coffee i", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Yeah, I can just imagine your dog covered in coffee grounds.  I dont know i", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 65, "question": " True, I guess thats right.  Maybe Ill try it on Champ and see if his fur looks better", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Probably not", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Yeah, I can just imagine your dog covered in coffee grounds.  I dont know i", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Oh, there was one other interesting use for coffee grounds  a cellulit", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Probably not", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " What!", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Oh, there was one other interesting use for coffee grounds  a cellulit", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Yeah, it said you were supposed to mix warm coffee grounds with olive oil an", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 78, "question": " What!", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " That sounds crazy", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Yeah, it said you were supposed to mix warm coffee grounds with olive oil an", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " I know, but lots of beauty products have caffeine in them.  So, it just migh", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 83, "question": " That sounds crazy", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " We should try it this weekend.  Its worth a shot", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 87, "question": " I know, but lots of beauty products have caffeine in them.  So, it just migh", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " OK, lets try it", "docId": "10-06", "aSentId": 88, "question": " We should try it this weekend.  Its worth a shot", "qSentId": 87}]
